{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "Answer: tied", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["Sometime", "and", "a", "tied"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["that", "him", "search", "to"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: and", "question": "In the following sentence identify Coordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["lifted", "The", "and", "him"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: After", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["a", "to", "After", "went"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["they", "the", "to", "of"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: few", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["few", "captured", "Sometime", "to"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: zoo", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["that", "in", "zoo", "take"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: later", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["tree", "a", "later", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: being", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (present participle).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["him", "let", "paw", "being"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: lifted", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["the", "go", "lifted", "that"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: lion", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["a", "lion", "tied", "to"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: able", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["the", "by", "lifted", "able"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: that", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["he", "The", "being", "that"]}], "success": 1}